export const Questions = [
  {
    question: "JavaScript is a",
    points: 10,
    options: {
      1: "Programming Language",
      2: "Online image editor",
      3: "Translation tool",
      4: "A platform to upload images",
    },
    correct: 1,
  },

  {
    question: "How we can initialize a empty node package ?",
    points: 5,
    options: {
      1: "Npm initialize",
      2: "new npm-init",
      3: "npm init",
      4: "init-npm",
    },
    correct: 3,
  },

  {
    question: "To build a react app you must type: ",
    points: 5,
    options: {
      1: "npv --react build",
      2: "npm run build",
      3: "npx react -build",
      4: "build react-app",
    },
    correct: 2,
  },

  {
    question: "Jest is a: ",
    points: 5,
    options: {
      1: "Network manager",
      2: "OpenSource platform",
      3: "A testing framework for JavaScript",
      4: "A modern browser",
    },
    correct: 3,
  },

  {
    question: "With PHP we can create",
    points: 8,
    options: {
      1: "Web applications",
      2: "Online tools for databases",
      3: "PDF",
      4: "Front-end applications",
    },
    correct: 1,
  },

  {
    question: "Who is the required tag for HTML document ?",
    points: 5,
    options: {
      1: "Image",
      2: "Head",
      3: "Footer",
      4: "All of theese",
    },
    correct: 2,
  },

  {
    question: "Which of those are Databases ?",
    points: 5,
    options: {
      1: "Node",
      2: "Redis",
      3: "Python",
      4: "CorelDraw",
    },
    correct: 2,
  },

  {
    question: "How many variables we can declare in JavaScript ?",
    points: 5,
    options: {
      1: "5",
      2: "3",
      3: "10",
      4: "Unlimited",
    },
    correct: 4,
  },

  {
    question: "The True datatype is",
    points: 3,
    options: {
      1: "Boolean",
      2: "Integer",
      3: "String",
      4: "Float",
    },
    correct: 1,
  },

  {
    question: "Which of those are frontend tool ?",
    points: 3,
    options: {
      1: "MongoDB",
      2: "Python",
      3: "Webpack",
      4: "Composer",
    },
    correct: 3,
  },

  {
    question:
      "To install a dependecies from packages.json you have to run this",
    points: 3,
    options: {
      1: "install-dependencies",
      2: "Npm add dependencies",
      3: "Npm install",
      4: "Npm autodep",
    },
    correct: 3,
  },

  {
    question: "To create a HTML5 project you need to install",
    points: 3,
    options: {
      1: "Notepad++",
      2: "Visual Studio Code",
      3: "Sublime Text",
      4: "One of this editors",
    },
    correct: 4,
  },

  {
    question: "What is the OOPs concept ?",
    points: 10,
    options: {
      1: "An alternative for DOM",
      2: "This is a best way for debuging",
      3: "Is a paradigm that provides concepts such as objects, classes, and inheritance.",
      4: "Some kind of unit testing",
    },
    correct: 3,
  },

  {
    question: "What are the important categories of software?",
    points: 10,
    options: {
      1: "System software",
      2: "Artificial Intelligence software",
      3: "Scientific software",
      4: "All of theese",
    },
    correct: 4,
  },

  {
    question: "Which of those is a software analysis & design tool",
    points: 5,
    options: {
      1: "Data Flow Diagrams",
      2: "SQL injection",
      3: "Version control",
      4: "Express.js",
    },
    correct: 1,
  },

  {
    question: "Which of those are not Unix command ?",
    points: 8,
    options: {
      1: "chmod",
      2: "mkdir",
      3: "finger",
      4: "deploy",
    },
    correct: 4,
  },

  {
    question: "Which of those is not valid CSS property ?",
    points: 8,
    options: {
      1: "background-color",
      2: "margin-left",
      3: "display-none",
      4: "border-box",
    },
    correct: 3,
  },

  {
    question: "The Docker is a",
    points: 10,
    options: {
      1: "command for test your code",
      2: "software platform that allows you to build, test, and deploy applications quickly",
      3: "database connection library",
      4: "design tool like PHotoshop",
    },
    correct: 2,
  },

  {
    question: "A valid Readme file for GitHub repo is",
    points: 4,
    options: {
      1: "README.cfg",
      2: "README",
      3: "README.txt",
      4: "README.md",
    },
    correct: 4,
  },
];
